retirementjobs.com 2009-08-22

# ABOUT US - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

RetirementJobs.com Privacy Policy  
RetirementJobs.com gathers information from site visitors from time to time to enhance existing services or provide additional services. RetirementJobs.com does not make this information available to third parties.

Uses of the information  
RetirementJobs.com uses the information it collects for internal purposes to develop products and services better suited to the needs of its users. RetirementJobs.com specifically asks for information about users who participate in site surveys, who sign up for one of RetirementJobs.com’s offerings, or who make a specific request, so as to fulfill those services. RetirementJobs.com may also use that information to alert users about additional products and services in which those users might be interested.

Disclosure to RetirementJobs.com partners  
RetirementJobs.com does not provide detailed information about individual site visits, nor the information users provide, to outside companies without users’ permission. RetirementJobs.com may share aggregated information about the use of this site to companies with which RetirementJobs.com has business relationships. This usage information, such as numbers and frequency of visits, is used to attract appropriate advertisers to various areas of the site. RetirementJobs.com provides this data so that advertisers and other businesses can better understand how people use partners’ content and the RetirementJobs.com site, with the goal of providing the best possible Web experience.

Privacy policies of other websites  
This site contains links to other sites. RetirementJobs.com at [www.RetirementJobs.com](http://www.retirementjobs.com/) is not responsible for the privacy practices nor the content of other sites, including integrated third-party advertisements.

Third-party ad servers RetirementJobs.com does not currently partner with or have special relationships with any third-party ad server companies to serve or present the ads that appear on the RetirementJobs.com destination website. However, some of our advertisers may use the services of third-party ad networks to serve or present certain ads that appear on the RetirementJobs.com destination website.

Privacy policy changes RetirementJobs.com reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. All changes will be posted on this page to inform our users what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

Contacting RetirementJobs.com If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please send correspondence to the following address:

Web Policy   
RetirementJobs.com   
204 Second Ave   
Waltham, MA 02451   

Update effective April, 2007

| 

CONTACT US RetirementJobs.com, Inc.  
204 Second Avenue  
Waltham, MA 02451

Sales & Pricing  
(781) 890-5050 (option 2)  

Job Seeker Inquiries  

Press Inquiries:  
Patrick Rafter  
(781) 890-5050 (option 4)
